<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<feed>
  <title>Creighton University Calendar</title>
  <description>Creighton University Calendar Feed</description>
  <link>http://calendar.creighton.edu</link>
  <events>
    <event>
      <date>May 21, 2014 8:00 am</date>
      <title>Chris is declared a winner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Seminar is designed to bring community and academia together to eliminate health disparities. The goal of the conference will be to discuss reasons for asthma disease disparities and explore solutions with community leaders. At the end of this workshop, the participant will be able to: summarize asthma health disparities; identify community, workplace, and health professional challenges in promoting asthma health equality; understand community-based approaches to preventing and responding to asthma health disparities; explain ethics and public policy issues in addressing asthma disease disparities. Continuing Education Credits: Continuing education credits are being offered: http://healthsciences.creighton.edu/addressing-health-disparities-focus-asthma<br />Registration: Please Register By Monday, April 21, 2014 online at http://2014asthma.eventbrite.com]]></description>
      <link>http://calendar.creighton.edu/event?id=43714</link>
      <event_id>43714</event_id>
      <calendar_id>3</calendar_id>
    </event>
    <event>
      <date>Apr 21, 2015 5:00 pm</date>
      <title>Addressing Health Disparities: Focus on Asthma</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The seminar is designed to bring community and academia together to eliminate health disparities. The goal of the conference will be to discuss reasons for asthma disease disparities and explore solutions with community leaders. At the end of this workshop, the participant will be able to: summarize asthma health disparities; identify community, workplace, and health professional challenges in promoting asthma health equality; understand community-based approaches to preventing and responding to asthma health disparities; explain ethics and public policy issues in addressing asthma disease disparities. Continuing Education Credits: Continuing education credits are being offered: http://healthsciences.creighton.edu/addressing-health-disparities-focus-asthma<br />Registration: Please Register By Monday, April 21, 2014 online at http://2014asthma.eventbrite.com]]></description>
      <link>http://calendar.creighton.edu/event?id=9077</link>
      <event_id>9077</event_id>
      <calendar_id>3,5</calendar_id>
    </event>
    <event>
      <date>Oct 21, 2014 8:00 am</date>
      <title>Jimmy Johns is Really Fast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Duck seminar is designed to bring community and academia together to eliminate health disparities. The goal of the conference will be to discuss reasons for asthma disease disparities and explore solutions with community leaders. At the end of this workshop, the participant will be able to: summarize asthma health disparities; identify community, workplace, and health professional challenges in promoting asthma health equality; understand community-based approaches to preventing and responding to asthma health disparities; explain ethics and public policy issues in addressing asthma disease disparities. Continuing Education Credits: Continuing education credits are being offered: http://healthsciences.creighton.edu/addressing-health-disparities-focus-asthma<br />Registration: Please Register By Monday, April 21, 2014 online at http://2014asthma.eventbrite.com]]></description>
      <link>http://calendar.creighton.edu/event?id=6312</link>
      <event_id>6312</event_id>
      <calendar_id>2,4,6,8,10</calendar_id>
    </event>
  </events>
</feed>